https://www.cmcu.com.au/about_cmcu/privacy_policy/

LocationsDisclaimerFormsBSB 803188'Better Service Banking'Internet banking login >
Home » About CMCU » Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyPrivacy
We are committed to ensuring the privacy of your personal information.
Like all other financial institutions, we are bound by the Australian Privacy Principles in the Privacy Act 1998 (Cth), and our staff have been trained to respect your privacy in accordance with this legislation.
We will collect personal information from you when you fill out an application or when you give us information over the phone. However, we may also collect your personal information form third parties. A common example of this is when we obtain information about your credit history (from a credit reporting agency) should you apply for a loan.
From time to time, we may disclose your personal information to other organisations. If we do this, we will seek to ensure that his information is held or used consistently with the Australian Privacy Principles. Some examples of these other organisations include third party suppliers such as printers, posting services and our advisers.
You can download our Privacy Notifications and Privacy Policy below:
Privacy Policy
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice Lending
Allianz Privacy Policy
Allianz Privacy Notice
Navigation
Home
About Us
Insurance
Financial Plans
Foreign Currency
Contact
Osko
Yarrawonga03 5744 371358 Belmore StYarrawonga, Victoria 3730info@cmcu.com.auSitemap | 2002 - 2020 © Central Murray Credit Union - Yarrawonga & Tungamah | www.cmcu.com.au - All Rights Reserved | Design by UBC Web Design
